The drug lords have the power, the money, the
connections. They didn't count on McBain
McBain is a action, war, drama film directed by James Glickenhaus.
Santos attempts to lead a people's revolt in
Colombia to overthrow the Presidente.
When his revolt fails and he is killed, his sister Christina goes to New York to
find McBain, a lieutenant Santos rescued during the Vietnam War.
McBain agrees to help, recruits his old war buddies, raises some cash by killing a few
drug dealers, then leads an attack to topple the Colombian government.
McBain, played by Christopher Walken.
Frank Bruce, played by Michael Ironside.
Major Tenny, played by Michael Joseph DeSare.
Roberto Santos, played by Chick Vennera.
Eastland, played by Steve James.
Gill, played by Thomas G. Waites.
McBain is a 1991 American action war film written and directed by James Glickenhaus, and starring
Christopher Walken as the title character, alongside Michael Ironside and María Conchita Alonso.
The film explores themes of mercenary, coup d'etat, revenge.
The tone is emotional.